Guide to the Afro-American Cultural Center at Yale Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Afro-American Cultural Center records, 1967-2006; Accession 2006-A-225
  - Black College Vote at Yale, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Black Screen, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Black Male's Discussion Group, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Black Political Forum, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Blaze Concert, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - BSMP, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Black Undergraduate Law Association, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Yale Caribbean AIDS Relief Effort, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Children's Center Mentorship Program, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Collective and Self Empowerment, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Ebonix, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - HEKAH Theater Ensemble, 1993-2003 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - In the Eyes of God, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - King's Men, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Student of Color for Reproductive Health, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - When Black Men Talk, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - WERC Theater, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - ZETA Phi Beta sorority, Inc., 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Black Pride Union [BPU], 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Black Solidarity Day, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - 1st Annual Black Solidarity Conference [BSC], 1995 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - 2nd Annual Black Solidarity Conference [BSC], 1996 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - 3rd Annual Black Solidarity Conference [BSC], 1997 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - 4th Annual Black Solidarity Conference [BSC], 1998 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - 5th Annual Black Solidarity Conference [BSC], 1999 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - 6th Annual Black Solidarity Conference [BSC], 2000 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - 7th Annual Black Solidarity Conference [BSC], 2001 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - 8th Annual Black Solidarity Conference [BSC], 2002 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - 10th Annual Black Solidarity Conference [BSC], 2004 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - 11th Annual Black Solidarity Conference [BSC], 2006 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Concerned Black Affiliates of Yale [Letter], 200? (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - UIC Memos of Understanding, 2001, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Anti-Racism Group, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - House programs and events
  - Flyers and programs, 1975-1981 (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Flyers and programs, 1982-1989 (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - Yale-Harvard, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - Flyers and programs, 1990-1995 (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - Flyers and programs, 1996-1999 (Box 3, Folder 167)
  - Events schedule, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - African Diaspora Summer Travel Fellowship, Undated (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - Flyers and programs, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - African Film Festival, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - Ten Thousand Tongues, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - Flyers and programs, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - Flyers and programs, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - Panther Film Festival, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - Queer People of Color - varied, 2001, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - Life 101, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - Flyers and programs, 2003-2005 (Box 3, Folder 178 - 180)
  - Achievement Awards Dinner programs, 1982-2006 (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - Flyers and programs, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - Flyers and programs, 1980s-1990s (Box 3, Folder 183)
  - Flyers and programs, 2000s (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - New Haven Community Outreach programs
  - The Company of Poets, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - Directory of New Haven Community Organizations, Undated (Box 3, Folder 186)
  - Correspondence - Books to Prison [request], Undated (Box 3, Folder 187)
  - Million Man March, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 188)
  - Black Man Think Tank, 10th Annual Conference, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 189)
  - Association of Black Culture Centers, 10th Annual Conference, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - Local Newspapers [Sample], 1999, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 191)
  - Blacks in Higher Education and in Society, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 192)
  - National Directory of African American Organizations, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 193)
  - Correspondence, Programs, 1977-2006 (Box 3, Folder 194)
  - Yale Campus and Physical Plant
  - Yale Campus - Stabbing Incident, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 195)
  - Medical Sciences Minority Recruitment Kit, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 196)
  - Outreach -Proposal, …Minority students in the health profs., 1999 (Box 3, Folder 197)
  - Tercentennial Celebrations, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 198)
  - Commitment to Equity [Athletics Report], 200? (Box 3, Folder 199)
  - Frederic Douglass Book Prize Kit, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 200)
  - Women's Center, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 201)
  - Yale Graduate School ["In the Company of Scholars"] Booklet, Undated (Box 3, Folder 202)
  - Yale, "Celebrating Diversity" Booklet, Undated (Box 3, Folder 203)
  - Cultural Connections, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 204)
  - Physical Plant
  - Security Alarm, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 205)
  - Renovations, 200? (Box 3, Folder 206)
  - Renovations Superstructure Engineers, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 207)
  - Alumni
  - Yale Alumni Associates of Afro-America…, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 208)
  - Bernice Cosey Pulley, Newspaper Clippings on MLK at Yale, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 209)
  - 15th Anniversary, Reflections on Black Life at Yale, 1983, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 210)
  - Lists of House Staff, African American Faculty - varied, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 211)
  - 15th Anniversary varied material, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 212)
  - African American Alumni -correspondence, programs, lists, 1985, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 213)
  - Kathleen N. Cleaver as Bunting Fellow [correspondence], 1994 (Box 3, Folder 214)
  - 25th Anniversary [Tentative] Plan of Events, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 215)
  - 25th Anniversary exhibit captions, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - 25th Anniversary correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - Jesse Rhines - Black Harvard, Black Yale - letter to alumni, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - Garry Reeder, "Black and Blue at Yale" [Prospectus], 1999 (Box 3, Folder 219)
  - Correspondence - gifts and pledges, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 220)
  - Gifts and pledges [5 Years for the House Initiative], 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - Gifts and pledges [5 Years for the House Initiative], 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - AACC fact sheet, 200? (Box 3, Folder 223)
  - Correspondence, minutes/notes at Yale Club in NYC, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - Yale Black Alumni -correspondence, minutes…, 1981-2000 (Box 3, Folder 225)
  - Arthur L. and Bernice Cosey Pulley, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - Kurt Schmoke -Levi Jackson, New York Times Obituary Clip, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - Vera Wells -Sylvia A. Boone, Memorial and Prize [correspondence], 2001 (Box 3, Folder 228)
  - African American Studies -correspondence, Directory, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 229)
  - AYA and Yale University Office of Development, 1990, 1994-2002 (Box 3, Folder 230)
  - Brian Hodge and Bennie Johnson -Xinobe Assoc. Newsletter, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 231)
  - African American Studies Alumni Reunion/Conference, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 232)
  - The Voice and Black Acts Blue Laws, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - Yale Blues -The Black Alumni Newsletter, 1996, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 235)
  - Director Correspondence -Varied [Goff-Crews], 1981-1997 (Box 4, Folder 236)
  - Edward A. Bouchet Tombstone, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 237)
  - Correspondence -Letters of [Gifts and Pledges and] Appreciation, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 238)
  - Correspondence -Endowment for the AACC, 1990-1991, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 239)
  - Study of Black Yale Alumni from the 1970s…, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 240)
  - Onaje Jackson, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 241)
  - 35th Anniversary Flyers, YDN Articles, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 242)
  - 35th Anniversary, Preps, Participants List, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 243)
  - 5 Years for the House Initiative, correspondence - Gifts and Pledges., 2000-02, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 244)
  - African American Activities after Graduation, 1998-2005 (Box 4, Folder 245)
  - Newspaper Clippings
  - 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 246)
  - 1984-1999 (Box 4, Folder 247)
  - 1990s (Box 4, Folder 248)
  - 2000 (Box 4, Folder 249)
  - 2001 (Box 4, Folder 250)
  - 2002 (Box 4, Folder 251)
  - [Online Response to YDN Article on Amiri Baraka's Visit], 2003 (Box 4, Folder 252)
  - 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 253)
  - House Publications
  - Golden Drum, Black Seeds, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 254)
  - Third World Voice, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 255)
  - Jesse A. Young, "A Century of Blacks at Yale…" manuscript, 1977? (Box 4, Folder 256)
  - 211 Park Street, The People's Paper, Black Ivy, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 257)
  - Varied, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 258)
  - 211 Park Street, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 259)
  - 211 Park Street [and Other Publications], 1984-1989 (Box 4, Folder 260)
  - 211 Park Street, 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 261)
  - 211 Park Street, 1990-1997 (Box 4, Folder 262)
  - Varied, 1995, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 263)
  - Black Ivy, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 264)
  - Reflection, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 265)
  - Jesse Rhines, "Living Memory" Manuscripts, 35th Anniversary Program, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 266)
  - Sphere, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 267)
  - Literate Soul and TYPE, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 268)
  - 211 Park Street, 2000-2005 (Box 4, Folder 269)
  - Sphere, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 270)